<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Signals from Mars</string>
    <string name="key_name">name</string>
    <string name="start_your_adventure">START YOUR ADVENTURE</string>
    <string name="signals_from_mars_title_image">Signals from Mars title image</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>

    <string name="page0">On your return trip from studying Saturns Rings, you hear a strange signal coming from Mars\.It is strange because there hasn\'t been a colony on Mars for years.\ Stranger yet is the fact that the signal is calling you by name:"Help me, %1$s, youre my only hope\    </string>
    <string name="page0_choice1">STOP AND INVESTIGATE</string>
    <string name="page0_choice2">CONTINUE HOME TO EARTH</string>

    <string name="page1">You deftly land your ship near where the distress signal originated. You didn\'t notice anything strange on your fly-by, but there is a cave in front of you. Behind you is an abandoned rover from the arly 21st century   </string>
    <string name="page1_choice1">EXPLORE THE CAVE</string>
    <string name="page1_choice2">EXPLORE THE ROVER</string>

    <string name="page2">You continue your course to Earth. Two days later, you receive a transmission from HQ saying that they have detected some sort of anomaly on the surface of Mars near an abandoned rover. They ask you to investigate, but ultimately the decision is yours because your mission has alraedy run much longer than planned and the supplies are running low.</string>
    <string name="page2_choice1">HEAD BACK TO MARS INVESTIGATE</string>
    <string name="page2_choice2">CONTINUE HOME TO EARTH</string>

    <string name="page3">Your EVA suit is equipped with a headlamp, which you use to navigate to a cave. After searching for a while, your oxygen levels are running pretty low. You know you should go refill your tank but there is a faint light up ahead.</string>
    <string name="page3_choice1">CONTINUE TOWARDS THE FAINT LIGHT</string>
    <string name="page3_choice2">REFILL AT SHIP AND EXPLORE THE ROVER</string>

    <string name="page4">The rover is covered in dust and most of the solar panels are broken. But you are quite surprised to see that the onbaord system is booted up and running. In fact, there is a message on the screen: \"%1$s, come to 28.543436,-81.369031." Those coordinates aren\'t far, but you do not know whether your oxygen will last there and back. </string>
    <string name="page4_choice1">EXPLORE THE COORDINATES</string>
    <string name="page4_choice2">RETURN TO EARTH</string>

    <string name="page5">After a long walk slightly uphill, you end up at the top of a small crater. You look around and are overjoyed to see your favourite android, %1$s -S1124. It had been lost on a previous mission to Mars! You take it back to your ship and fly back to Earth./ </string>


    <string name="page6">You arrive home on Earth. While your mission was a success, you forever wonder what was sending that signal. Perhaps a future mission will be able to investigate.....</string>
    <string name="story_image_content_desccription">Story Page image</string>
    <string name="play_again_button_text">PLAY AGAIN</string>


</resources>
